Artem Shchirov

Web Developer

Contact

Address

Israel

Phone

+972584441705

E-mail

artemshchirov@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/artemshchirov/

www

https://artemshchirov.github .io/portfolio/

Skills

HTML

CSS, Sass, BEM

JavaScript, TypeScript

DOM, OOP, REST API

Webpack

React.js, Redux

Node.js, Express.js, NestJS

Nginx

SQL, MongoDB

Firebase

Git, GitHub

Python

Teamwork

I am a Web Developer oriented on creating user-centered web apps based on modern dev methodologies and products that serve users' needs in creative and efficient ways.

My aim as a developer during coding is to keep my codes sleek and always human-understandable.

My daily task is to be equipped with the right knowledge and tools to enable me achieve these as I code.

Work History

2021-09 -2022-09

Student Web Developer

Practicum Israel

- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML and CSS
- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers and operating systems
- Adapted quickly to constantly changing, deadline-driven environment
- Attended development programs to gain competencies and boost skills set
- Worked closely with developers on creating new code

2021-09 -Current

Madrich

The Jewish Agency For Israel

- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties.
- Demonstrated respect, friendliness and willingness to help wherever needed.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.

2020-12 -2021-12

Security at Ministry of Health Care

Duvdevan, Israel

- Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately
- Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions

Software

Visual Studio Code

Postman

Figma

Linux

Languages

English

Hebrew

Russian

Ukrainian

2018-12 -2020-12

First Aid Provider

Duvdevan, Israel

- Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately
- Kept up with continuing education requirements to maintain certification
- Communicated clearly and openly with dispatch to receive new orders and convey important updates about scenes

Education

2021-09 -2022-09

Junior Web Developer

Practicum Israel

Practice and achievements

- Went through code review.
- Worked regularly with a mentor.
- Worked in a team on freelance projects.
- An senior student who accompanies newcomers in learning.
- Continuing education in Web Development

2020-05 -Current

Programming

Self Education

- TypeScript
- Firebase
- NestJS
- Python
- Linux

2020-09 -

Madrich: Education

Current

The Jewish Agency For Israel - Israel

- Member of volunteers for Jewish Agency for Israel
- Received a Madrich diploma
- Continuing education in Education

2015-11 -2018-11

First Aid: Medicine

Israel Defense Forces - Israel

- Elected to sergeant for IDF in 2016
- ability to communicate with different people
- responsibility for decisions made
- first aid: physical and mental

Interests

Volunteering

Arduino, Raspberry Pi

Books

Pet projects

About

I have been in love with programming and technology since high school.

I began doing web development because I like to create web products and I wanted to do this 24/7.

Meetups, online conferences, hackathons — I participate everywhere whenever possible. In Yandex.Practicum I was lucky to become a senior student. I have gained experience by working with other programmers.

Also I like code games and apps for fun, "Grokking Algorithms" and "Grokking Deep Learning" out of curiosity, if, of course, there is time left after learning TypeScript and pet projects.

- Fond of Codewars and Leetcode.
- Building a drone according to guides I found on YouTube, on Raspberry Pi and Python.
- Sports and a healthy style life.
- Volunteer (for example, as a counselor at summer camps in the CIS).